Guide to the Time Inc. Time Editorial Records 1938-2009 MS 3009-RG 7
New-York Historical Society
- Series III.A. Art Department: Cover Researcher Rosemary Frank Files, 1948-2009 (bulk 1963-1988); 20 Linear feet in 20 record cartons
  - Subseries III.A.2. Artist Files, 1948-2009 (bulk 1963-1988); 18 Linear feet in 18 record cartons
    - Hull, Cathy (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 1)
    - Hunter, Stan (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 2)
    - Husain, M. F. (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 3)
    - Ikeda, Shig (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 4)
    - Illingworth, Tim (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 5)
    - Immigration Cover (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 6)
    - Immigration Cover [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Indiana, Robert (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 7)
    - Inouye, Carol (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 8)
    - Jackson, Harry (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 9)
    - Jaffe, Mark (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 10)
    - Jamara, Mario (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 11)
    - Jampel, Judith (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 12)
    - Jarvis, David W. (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 13)
    - Jean, Carol (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 14)
    - Jennings, Comer (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 15)
    - Jensen, Ole (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 16)
    - Jezierski, Chet (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 17-18)
    - Jiminez, Luis (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 19)
    - Johns, John A. (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 20)
    - Johnson, David (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Doug (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 22)
    - Johnson, Michael (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 23)
    - Jones, Amy (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 24)
    - Jones, Bob (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 25)
    - Jones, Joe (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 26)
    - Jorg, Elizabeth (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 27)
    - Just, Hal (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 28)
    - Kahn, Al (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 29)
    - Kaisch, Luise (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 30)
    - Kalish, Lionel (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 31)
    - Kane, John (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 32)
    - Kanovitz, Howard (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 33)
    - Kappes, Werner (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 34)
    - Karchin, Steve (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 35)
    - Karim, Fazal (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 36)
    - Karlin, Eugene (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 37)
    - Kasprzycki, Jan (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 38)
    - Katayama, Nampu (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 39)
    - Katz, Alex (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 40-41)
    - Katz, Alex [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Katzman, H. (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 42)
    - Kazumi, Husein (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 43)
    - Kearney, John (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 44)
    - Keene, Paul S. Jr. (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 45)
    - Keillor (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 46)
    - Kent, Sister Mary Corita (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 47)
    - Kidd, Earl (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 48)
    - Kienholz, Edward (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 49)
    - Kilbride, Bob (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 50)
    - King, William (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 51)
    - Kingman, Dong (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 52)
    - Kinigstein, Jonah (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 53)
    - Kinstler, Everett Raymond (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 54)
    - Klapheck, Konrad (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 55)
    - Klarwein, Mathias (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 56)
    - Klein, Earl (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 57)
    - Kliros, Ted (Offsite-box 2565, Folder 58)
    - Koch, John (Offsite-box 857, Folder 1)
    - Kodansha Ltd. Publishers (Offsite-box 857, Folder 2)
    - Koehler, Henry (Offsite-box 857, Folder 3)
    - Koerner, Henry (Offsite-box 857, Folder 4)
    - Kokinos, Tony (Offsite-box 857, Folder 5)
    - Konz, Francesco (Offsite-box 857, Folder 6)
    - Koren, Ed (Offsite-box 857, Folder 7-8)
    - Koslow, Howard (Offsite-box 857, Folder 9)
    - Kossin, Sanford (Offsite-box 857, Folder 10)
    - Kouris, Michael (Offsite-box 857, Folder 11)
    - Kozak, George (Offsite-box 857, Folder 12)
    - Krieger, Bob (Offsite-box 857, Folder 13)
    - Kubinyi, Laszlo (Offsite-box 857, Folder 14)
    - Laderman, Gabriel (Offsite-box 857, Folder 15)
    - Lagarrigue, Jean (Offsite-box 857, Folder 16)
    - LaLiberte, Norman (Offsite-box 857, Folder 17-18)
    - Lambert, Jarvis (Offsite-box 857, Folder 19)
    - Lambert, Saul (Offsite-box 857, Folder 20)
    - Lawler, Dan (Offsite-box 857, Folder 21)
    - Lawrence, Jacob (Offsite-box 857, Folder 22)
    - Leake, Donald (Offsite-box 857, Folder 23)
    - Lee, Carol (Offsite-box 857, Folder 24)
    - Leedy, Jeff (Offsite-box 857, Folder 25)
    - Leffel, David A. (Offsite-box 857, Folder 26)
    - Leibowitz, Matthew (Offsite-box 857, Folder 27)
    - Leifer, Neil (Offsite-box 857, Folder 28)
    - Leonard, Michael (Offsite-box 857, Folder 29)
    - Leslie, Alfred (Offsite-box 857, Folder 30)
    - Let There Be Neon (Offsite-box 857, Folder 31)
    - Lettick, Birney (Offsite-box 857, Folder 32-33)
    - Levering, Bob (Offsite-box 857, Folder 34)
    - Levin, Arnie (Offsite-box 857, Folder 35)
    - Levine, David (Offsite-box 857, Folder 36-37)
    - Levine, Jack (Offsite-box 857, Folder 38)
    - Levine, Ned (Offsite-box 857, Folder 39)
    - Levithan, Charles (Offsite-box 857, Folder 40)
    - Lewin, Ted (Offsite-box 857, Folder 41)
    - Lewis, Tim (Offsite-box 857, Folder 42)
    - Ley, Richard (Offsite-box 857, Folder 43)
    - Leydenfrost, Bob (Offsite-box 857, Folder 44)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy (Offsite-box 857, Folder 45)
    - Lidov, Arthur (Offsite-box 857, Folder 46)
    - Liepke, Skip (Offsite-box 857, Folder 47-48)
    - Lilly, Charles (Offsite-box 857, Folder 49)
    - Limbach, Hans Jörg (Offsite-box 857, Folder 50)
    - Linder, Richard (Offsite-box 857, Folder 51)
    - Lionetti, Frank (Offsite-box 857, Folder 52)
    - Lippman, Peter (Offsite-box 857, Folder 53)
    - Lodigensky, Ted (Offsite-box 857, Folder 54)
    - Lomonaco, Louis (Offsite-box 857, Folder 55)
    - Lorenz, Lee (Offsite-box 857, Folder 56)
    - Lorjou, Bernard (Offsite-box 857, Folder 57)
    - Luciana (Offsite-box 857, Folder 58)
    - Lundgren, Charles (Offsite-box 857, Folder 59)
    - Lurie, Ra'anan (Offsite-box 857, Folder 60)
    - MacDonald, Norman (Offsite-box 857, Folder 61)
    - Mack, Stan (Offsite-box 857, Folder 62)
    - Mackay, Don (Offsite-box 857, Folder 63)
    - MacKendrick, Lilian (Offsite-box 857, Folder 64)
    - Mackler, Tina (Offsite-box 857, Folder 65)
    - MacPherson, Duncan (Offsite-box 857, Folder 66-67)
    - Maffia, Daniel (Offsite-box 857, Folder 68-69)
    - Magagna, Anna Marie (Offsite-box 857, Folder 70)
    - Magee, Alan (Offsite-box 857, Folder 71)
    - Mahvrin, Matt (Offsite-box 857, Folder 72)
    - Maillart, Jean-Denis (Offsite-box 857, Folder 73)
    - Maitin, Samuel C. (Offsite-box 857, Folder 74)
    - Mandel, Saul (Offsite-box 857, Folder 75)
    - Manor, Jim (Offsite-box 857, Folder 76)
    - Mantel, Richard (Offsite-box 857, Folder 77)
    - Manzu, Giacomo (Offsite-box 857, Folder 78-79)
    - Marans, Moissaye (Offsite-box 857, Folder 80)
    - Marco, Phil (Offsite-box 857, Folder 81)
    - Marisol (Offsite-box 857, Folder 82)
    - Marcus, Marcia (Offsite-box 857, Folder 83)
    - Mardon, Alan (Offsite-box 857, Folder 84)
    - Marein, Shirley (Offsite-box 858, Folder 1)
    - Marguerita (Offsite-box 858, Folder 2)
    - Marguiles, Joseph (Offsite-box 858, Folder 3)
    - Mark, Mona (Offsite-box 858, Folder 4)
    - Markowitz, Henry (Offsite-box 858, Folder 5)
    - Marschall, Ken (Offsite-box 858, Folder 6)
    - Marsh, James (Offsite-box 858, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, Fred (Offsite-box 858, Folder 8)
    - Martel, Maria (Offsite-box 858, Folder 9)
    - Martin, David Stone (Offsite-box 858, Folder 10)
    - Martin, Knox (Offsite-box 858, Folder 11)
    - Marvin, Frederic (Offsite-box 858, Folder 12)
    - Mason, Frank (Offsite-box 858, Folder 13)
    - Mason, Phillip Lindsay (Offsite-box 858, Folder 14)
    - Mathieu, Dora (Offsite-box 858, Folder 15)
    - Maton, Charles and Gabriel Pascalini (Offsite-box 858, Folder 16)
    - Matta, Elizabeth (Offsite-box 858, Folder 17)
    - Matta, Roberto (Offsite-box 858, Folder 18)
    - Matthews, Paul (Offsite-box 858, Folder 19)
    - Mauldin, Bill (Offsite-box 858, Folder 20)
    - Max, Peter (Offsite-box 858, Folder 21)
    - Mayo, Frank (Offsite-box 858, Folder 22)
    - Mazeika, Anna (Offsite-box 858, Folder 23)
    - McAfee, Mara (Offsite-box 858, Folder 24)
    - McCall, Robert (Offsite-box 858, Folder 25)
    - McCance, Lewis (Offsite-box 858, Folder 26)
    - McClanahan, Marion (Offsite-box 858, Folder 27)
    - McCormick, Harry (Offsite-box 858, Folder 28)
    - McFall, David (Offsite-box 858, Folder 29)
    - McGee, Alan (Offsite-box 858, Folder 30)
    - McGhee, Charles (Offsite-box 858, Folder 31)
    - McGuggart, Judy (Offsite-box 858, Folder 32)
    - McInnerney, Mike (Offsite-box 858, Folder 33)
    - McIntosh, Bruce (Offsite-box 858, Folder 34)
    - McKay, Donald (Offsite-box 858, Folder 35)
    - McLean, Richard (Offsite-box 858, Folder 36)
    - McLean, Wilson (Offsite-box 858, Folder 37)
    - McMahon, Franklin (Offsite-box 858, Folder 38)
    - McMullan, Jim (Offsite-box 858, Folder 39)
    - McNalis, Jim (Offsite-box 858, Folder 40)
    - McNamara, Joseph (Offsite-box 858, Folder 41)
    - McQuaite, Karen (Offsite-box 858, Folder 42)
    - McVicker, Charles (Offsite-box 858, Folder 43)
    - Meiselman, Leonard (Offsite-box 858, Folder 44)
    - Melo, John (Offsite-box 858, Folder 45)
    - Mencone, Ralph (Offsite-box 858, Folder 46)
    - Mendez, Charles (Offsite-box 858, Folder 47)
    - Mengele Cover (Offsite-box 858, Folder 48)
    - Meola, Eric (Offsite-box 858, Folder 49)
    - Mesches, Arnold (Offsite-box 858, Folder 50)
    - Meyerowitz, Rick (Offsite-box 858, Folder 51)
    - Meyers, Newton (Offsite-box 858, Folder 52)
    - Midgette, Willard (Offsite-box 858, Folder 53)
    - Mihaesco, Eugene (Offsite-box 858, Folder 54-58)
    - Mikus, Victor (Offsite-box 858, Folder 59)
    - Minor, Wendell (Offsite-box 858, Folder 60)
    - Mitelberg, Louis (Offsite-box 858, Folder 61)
    - Miyake Cover (Offsite-box 858, Folder 62)
    - Miyamoto, Lance R. (Offsite-box 858, Folder 63)
    - Miyauchi, Haruo (Offsite-box 858, Folder 64)
    - Moment, John (Offsite-box 858, Folder 65)
    - Monroe, Bob (Offsite-box 858, Folder 66)
    - Mordvinoff, Nicolas (Offsite-box 858, Folder 67)
    - Morgan, Jacquin (Offsite-box 858, Folder 68)
    - Morgan, Maritza (Offsite-box 858, Folder 69)
    - Morley, Malcolm (Offsite-box 858, Folder 70)
    - Morris, Robert (Offsite-box 858, Folder 71)
    - Morrow, Tom (Offsite-box 858, Folder 72)
    - Moser, Lida (Offsite-box 858, Folder 73)
    - Moss, Don (Offsite-box 858, Folder 74)
    - Moss, Geoffrey (Offsite-box 858, Folder 75)
    - Moulton, Lee (Offsite-box 858, Folder 76)
    - Moxcey, Ralph (Offsite-box 858, Folder 77)
    - Mugnaini, Joe (Offsite-box 858, Folder 78)
    - Mulatier, Jean (Offsite-box 859, Folder 1)
    - Mullin, Willard (Offsite-box 859, Folder 2)
    - Mullins, Frank (Offsite-box 859, Folder 3)
    - Munro, Gordon (Offsite-box 859, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, John Cullen (Offsite-box 859, Folder 5)
    - Nagle, Pat (Offsite-box 859, Folder 6)
    - Nash, Carol (Offsite-box 859, Folder 7)
    - Neel, Alice (Offsite-box 859, Folder 8)
    - Neibart, Wally (Offsite-box 859, Folder 9)
    - Neiman, Leroy (Offsite-box 859, Folder 10)
    - Nelson, Bill (Offsite-box 859, Folder 11)
    - Nelson, Robert A. (Offsite-box 859, Folder 12)
    - Nemec, Verneta (Offsite-box 859, Folder 13)
    - Nesbitt, Lowell (Offsite-box 859, Folder 14)
    - Nevelson, Mike (Offsite-box 859, Folder 15)
    - Newcomb, John (Offsite-box 859, Folder 16)
    - Newman, Arnold (Offsite-box 859, Folder 17)
    - Newton, Helmut (Offsite-box 859, Folder 18)
    - Noble, Larry (Offsite-box 859, Folder 19)
    - Noland, Kenneth (Offsite-box 859, Folder 20)
    - Northern, Tony (Offsite-box 859, Folder 21)
    - Norton, John (Offsite-box 859, Folder 22)
    - Noges, David (Offsite-box 859, Folder 23)
    - Nye, Edgar (Offsite-box 859, Folder 24)
    - Oakes, Bill (Offsite-box 859, Folder 25)
    - Oberhardt, William (Offsite-box 859, Folder 26)
    - Oden, Dick (Offsite-box 859, Folder 27)
    - O'Hara, Patrick (Offsite-box 859, Folder 28)
    - O'Keefe, Georgia (Offsite-box 859, Folder 29)
    - Oldenburg, Claes (Offsite-box 859, Folder 30)
    - O'Leary, John (Offsite-box 859, Folder 31)
    - Oliphant, Patrick (Offsite-box 859, Folder 32-33)
    - Oliphant, Patrick [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Olson, Mimi Vang (Offsite-box 859, Folder 34)
    - Organ, Bryan (Offsite-box 859, Folder 35-36)
    - Orlina, Ramon G. (Offsite-box 859, Folder 37)
    - Ornati, Ernesto (Offsite-box 859, Folder 38)
    - Osborn, Robert (Offsite-box 859, Folder 39)
    - Osmurdsen, William Barth (Offsite-box 859, Folder 40)
    - Otnes, Fred (Offsite-box 859, Folder 41-42)
    - Pack, Frank (Offsite-box 859, Folder 43)
    - Palladini, David (Offsite-box 859, Folder 44)
    - Palulian, Dickran (Offsite-box 859, Folder 45)
    - Paolozzi, Eduardo (Offsite-box 859, Folder 46)
    - Park, William Bryan (Offsite-box 859, Folder 47-48)
    - Parker, Robert Andrew (Offsite-box 859, Folder 49)
    - Parks, Gordon (Offsite-box 859, Folder 50)
    - Pascalini, Gabriel (Offsite-box 859, Folder 51)
    - Peak, Bob (Offsite-box 859, Folder 52)
    - Pearlstein, Philip (Offsite-box 859, Folder 53-54)
    - Pearlstein, Philip [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Pearson, Drew (Offsite-box 859, Folder 55)
    - Perez, Vincent (Offsite-box 859, Folder 56)
    - Perlin, Bernard (Offsite-box 859, Folder 57)
    - Perlis, Donald (Offsite-box 859, Folder 58)
    - Pernish, Paul (Offsite-box 859, Folder 59)
    - Petragnani, Vincent (Offsite-box 859, Folder 60)
    - Petrucelli, A. (Offsite-box 860, Folder 1)
    - Petty, George (Offsite-box 860, Folder 2)
    - Pfrieum, Bernard (Offsite-box 860, Folder 3)
    - Phillips, James (Offsite-box 860, Folder 4)
    - Piccillo, Joseph (Offsite-box 860, Folder 5)
    - Picha (Walronens, Jean-Paul) (Offsite-box 860, Folder 6-7)
    - Pierce, Bill (Offsite-box 860, Folder 8)
    - Pike, Marion (Offsite-box 860, Folder 9)
    - Pimsler, Alvin J. (Offsite-box 860, Folder 10)
    - Pinkney, Jerry (Offsite-box 860, Folder 11)
    - Piper, Christian (Offsite-box 860, Folder 12)
    - Plattenberger (Offsite-box 860, Folder 13)
    - Plourde, David (Offsite-box 860, Folder 14)
    - Pollack, Reginald (Offsite-box 860, Folder 15)
    - Poor, Anne (Offsite-box 860, Folder 16-17)
    - Pond, Clayton (Offsite-box 860, Folder 18)
    - Porter, Fairfield (Offsite-box 860, Folder 19)
    - Poucette Murals (Offsite-box 860, Folder 20)
    - Powell, Ivan (Offsite-box 860, Folder 21)
    - Powell, William Nowland Van (Offsite-box 860, Folder 22)
    - Prestopino, Gregario (Offsite-box 860, Folder 23)
    - Pryor, Robert (Offsite-box 860, Folder 24-25)
    - Psychedelic Art and Artists (Offsite-box 860, Folder 26)
    - Pugh, Clifton (Offsite-box 860, Folder 27)
    - Pumpkin Artists (Offsite-box 860, Folder 28)
    - Punchatz, Don Ivan (Offsite-box 860, Folder 29)
    - Pyle, Liz (Offsite-box 860, Folder 30)
    - Rackow, Leo (Offsite-box 860, Folder 31)
    - Radulovic, Savo (Offsite-box 860, Folder 32)
    - Raffael, Joseph (Offsite-box 860, Folder 33)
    - Ramos, Mel (Offsite-box 860, Folder 34)
    - Ramus, Mike (Offsite-box 860, Folder 35)
    - Rauch, Hans-George (Offsite-box 860, Folder 36)
    - Rattner, Abraham (Offsite-box 860, Folder 37)
    - Ratzkin, Lawrence (Offsite-box 860, Folder 38)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert (Offsite-box 860, Folder 39)
    - Rebali, Joseph (Offsite-box 860, Folder 40)
    - Reingold, Alan (Offsite-box 860, Folder 41)
    - Reinhardt, Siegfried (Offsite-box 860, Folder 42)
    - Reynolds, Wade (Offsite-box 860, Folder 43)
    - Rhana, Lisa (Offsite-box 860, Folder 44)
    - Rhodes, Andrew (Offsite-box 860, Folder 45)
    - Brother Richard (Offsite-box 860, Folder 46)
    - Richards, Walter (Offsite-box 860, Folder 47)
    - Richardson/Smith (Offsite-box 860, Folder 48)
    - Riger, Robert (Offsite-box 860, Folder 49)
    - Rigg, Robert (Offsite-box 860, Folder 50)
    - Rindner, Jack N. (Offsite-box 860, Folder 51)
    - Rivera, Diego (Offsite-box 860, Folder 52)
    - Rivers, Larry (Offsite-box 860, Folder 53)
    - Rixford, Ellen (Offsite-box 860, Folder 54)
    - Robbins, Alan (Offsite-box 860, Folder 55)
    - Rockmare, Noel (Offsite-box 860, Folder 56)
    - Rockwell, Norman (Offsite-box 860, Folder 57)
    - Rodrigues, Clauco Octavio Castilhos (Offsite-box 860, Folder 58)
    - Rogers, Howard (Offsite-box 860, Folder 59)
    - Rojek, Christine (Offsite-box 860, Folder 60)
    - Rombola, John (Offsite-box 860, Folder 61)
    - Rose, William (Offsite-box 860, Folder 62)
    - Rose, Gerard de (Offsite-box 860, Folder 63)
    - Roseman, Stanley (Offsite-box 860, Folder 64)
    - Rosenquist, James (Offsite-box 860, Folder 65)
    - Rosenthal, Seymour (Offsite-box 860, Folder 66)
    - Ross, Larry (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 1)
    - Roth, Arnold (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 2)
    - Roth, Lother (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 3)
    - Rowe, Charles (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 4)
    - Rowe, Guy (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 5)
    - Rubin, Marvin (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 6)
    - Ruckle, Ernest (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 7)
    - Ruffins, Reynold (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 8)
    - Ruscha, Ed (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 9)
    - Sacks, Cal (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 10-11)
    - Sacks, Shelly (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 12)
    - Saco, Don (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 13)
    - Safran, Bernard (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 14)
    - Sagebrush (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 15)
    - Saito, Kiyoshi (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 16)
    - Samerjan, George (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 17)
    - Sanden, Howard (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 18)
    - Sanders, Bill (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 19)
    - Sanford (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 20)
    - Santore, Charles (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 21)
    - Sargent, Margaret Holland (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 22)
    - Savage, Steele (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 23)
    - Sawka, Jon (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 24)
    - Saxon, Charles (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 25)
    - Scarfe, Gerald (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 26-31)
    - Scavullo, Francesco [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Offsite-box R39)
    - Schaumann, Peter (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 32)
    - Schlecht, Richard (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 33)
    - Schleinkofer, David (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 34)
    - Schmidt, Harvey (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 35)
    - Schonzeit, Ben (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 36)
    - Schorr, Todd (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 37)
    - Schottland, Miriam (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 38)
    - Schrader, David (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 39)
    - Schrag, Karl (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 40)
    - Schreiter, Rick (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 41)
    - Schulenberg, Bob (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 42)
    - Schultz, Charles (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 43-45)
    - Schuster, Elle (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 46)
    - Schwartz, Daniel (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 47)
    - Scrofani, Joseph (Offsite-box 2587, Folder 48)
    - Searle, Ronald (Offsite-box 861, Folder 1)
    - Segal, Alex (Offsite-box 861, Folder 2)
    - Segal, George (Offsite-box 861, Folder 3-4)
    - Segall, Larry (Offsite-box 861, Folder 5)
    - Seidler, Sheldon (Offsite-box 861, Folder 6)
    - Seltzer, Isadora (Offsite-box 861, Folder 7)
    - Selz, Irma (Offsite-box 861, Folder 8)
    - Sendak, Maurice (Offsite-box 861, Folder 9)
    - Sevall, Sid (Offsite-box 861, Folder 10)
    - Sgouras, Thomas (Offsite-box 861, Folder 11)
    - Shahn, Ben (Offsite-box 861, Folder 12)
    - Sharpe, Jim (Offsite-box 861, Folder 13)
    - Shaw, Sherrill (Offsite-box 861, Folder 14)
    - Shea, Shawn (Offsite-box 861, Folder 15)
    - Sherman, Ivan (Offsite-box 861, Folder 16)
    - Shields, Bill (Offsite-box 861, Folder 17)
    - Shields, Charles (Offsite-box 861, Folder 18)
    - Shikler, Aaron (Offsite-box 861, Folder 19)
    - Shilstone, Arthur (Offsite-box 861, Folder 20)
    - Shore, Robert (Offsite-box 861, Folder 21)
    - Shuptrine, Hubert (Offsite-box 861, Folder 22)
    - Sidney Nolan (Offsite-box 861, Folder 23)
    - Siegel, Anita (Offsite-box 861, Folder 24)
    - Silverman, Burt (Offsite-box 861, Folder 25-26)
    - Simpson, Harvey (Offsite-box 861, Folder 27)
    - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (SITES) (Offsite-box 861, Folder 28)
    - Sklenar, Fred (Offsite-box 861, Folder 29)
    - Skogsbergh, Ulf (Offsite-box 861, Folder 30)
    - Slackman, Chas B. (Offsite-box 861, Folder 31)
    - Slater, Frank (Offsite-box 861, Folder 32)
    - Sleigh, Sylvia (Offsite-box 861, Folder 33)
    - Sloan, Robert (Offsite-box 861, Folder 34)
    - Slonevsky, Leonard (Offsite-box 861, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Joseph A. (Offsite-box 861, Folder 36)
    - Smollin, Michael (Offsite-box 861, Folder 37)
    - Sochurek, Howard (Offsite-box 861, Folder 38)
    - Solman, Joseph (Offsite-box 861, Folder 39)
    - Solovioff, Nick (Offsite-box 861, Folder 40)
    - Sorel, Ed (Offsite-box 861, Folder 41)
    - Sovjani, John (Offsite-box 861, Folder 42)
    - Soger, Moses (Offsite-box 861, Folder 43)
    - Soger, Raphael (Offsite-box 861, Folder 44)
    - Spanfeller, James (Offsite-box 861, Folder 45)
    - Sparks, Richard (Offsite-box 861, Folder 46)
    - Der Spiegel (John White) (Offsite-box 861, Folder 47)
    - Spina, Paul (Offsite-box 861, Folder 48)
    - Sposato, John (Offsite-box 861, Folder 49)
    - Stabin, Victor (Offsite-box 861, Folder 50)
    - Stacey, Gloria (Offsite-box 861, Folder 51)
    - Stark, Bruce (Offsite-box 861, Folder 52)
    - Starkman, Sheldon (Offsite-box 861, Folder 53)
    - Steele, Mark (Offsite-box 861, Folder 54)
    - Steig, William (Offsite-box 861, Folder 55)
    - Stein, David (Offsite-box 861, Folder 56)
    - Stein, Ronald (Offsite-box 861, Folder 57)
    - Steinberg, Saul (Offsite-box 861, Folder 58-59)
    - Steptoe, John (Offsite-box 861, Folder 60)
    - Stermer, Dugald (Offsite-box 862, Folder 1)
    - Stern, Bernard (Offsite-box 862, Folder 2)
    - Sternglass, Arno (Offsite-box 862, Folder 3)
    - Stivers, Don (Offsite-box 862, Folder 4)
    - Storey, Barron (Offsite-box 862, Folder 5)
    - Strinbam, Robert (Offsite-box 862, Folder 6)
    - Suares, Jean-Claude (Offsite-box 862, Folder 7)
    - Suter, David (Offsite-box 862, Folder 8)
    - Sutherland, Graham (Offsite-box 862, Folder 9)
    - Szafran, Gene (Offsite-box 862, Folder 10)
    - Taddeo, John (Offsite-box 862, Folder 11)
    - Tadnick, Leon (Offsite-box 862, Folder 12)
    - Tallon, Robert (Offsite-box 862, Folder 13)
    - Tamayo, Rufino (Offsite-box 862, Folder 14)
    - Tauss, Herb (Offsite-box 862, Folder 15)
    - Templeton, Robert (Offsite-box 862, Folder 16)
    - Teraoka, Masami (Offsite-box 862, Folder 17-18)
    - Terpning, Howard (Offsite-box 862, Folder 19)
    - Thiebaud, Wayne (Offsite-box 862, Folder 20)
    - Thollander, Earl (Offsite-box 862, Folder 21)
    - Thompson, Don (Offsite-box 862, Folder 22)
    - Thompson, Richard (Offsite-box 862, Folder 23)
    - Tinkelman, Murray (Offsite-box 862, Folder 24)
    - Tobey, Alton (Offsite-box 862, Folder 25)
    - Tomlinson, Richard (Offsite-box 862, Folder 26)
    - Tooker, George (Offsite-box 862, Folder 27)
    - Topalski, Felikse (Offsite-box 862, Folder 28)
    - Topar, Roland (Offsite-box 862, Folder 29)
    - Torres, John, Jr. (Offsite-box 862, Folder 30)
    - Trachtman, Arnold (Offsite-box 862, Folder 31)
    - Treatner, Meryl (Offsite-box 862, Folder 32)
    - Trog (Offsite-box 862, Folder 33)
    - Trova, Ernest (Offsite-box 862, Folder 34)
    - Trudeau, Garry (Offsite-box 862, Folder 35)
    - Tsuchihashi, Hiroko (Offsite-box 862, Folder 36)
    - Turner, Pete (Offsite-box 862, Folder 37)
    - Turner, Pete [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Ulbricht, John (Offsite-box 862, Folder 38)
    - Underhill, Slayton (Offsite-box 862, Folder 39)
    - Ungerer, Tomi (Offsite-box 862, Folder 40)
    - Unknown artist negatives (Offsite-box 862, Folder 41)